JUNWEN CHEN

0406-226-809 mayjunwenchen@gmail.com junwenchen.com



I'm a Full-Stack Developer and Experience Designer.

I'm passionate about building empathy with people, and designing satisfying experiences for them. I enjoy development as it makes things happen and brings design to life.

EXPERIENCE

Designer & Front-End Developer

JXT Global (Digital Agency) Aug 2017 - Dec 2017 Worked closely with the design & front-end teams
Designed marketing materials (brochures/banners, etc)
Designed responsive websites with branding guidelines
Coded the website front-end with Javascript
Coded EDMs

Full-Stack Developer

Pacific Magazines Feb 2018 - Present Developed CMS/digital publishing/E-commerce platforms Worked on front-end(Javascript) and back-end(.Net/C#) Worked in Agile & Scrum environment Conducted QA tasks

EDUCATION

Master of Interaction Design

The University of Sydney July 2016 - June 2018 Designed solutions with user-centred methods Prototyped with programming languages Developed solid user research and design thinking skills

Bachelor of Information Security

China University of Mining and Technology Sept 2012 - June 2016 Gained solid knowledge on computer science basics Gained solid knowledge on programming fundamentals Developed strong problem solving and reasoning skills

SKILLS

